[('PERSON', 'Well'), ('GPE', 'Muslims')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'HDFC'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ATM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Private Banks'), ('GPE', 'Public'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ICICI')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Card'), ('PERSON', 'Cash'), ('PERSON', 'Dinner'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Ambassador'), ('GPE', 'Cant')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Deepak'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FDI'), ('PERSON', 'Saab'), ('PERSON', 'Kumar Sharma Saab'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GST')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Communist')]
[('GPE', 'Rss')]
[('PERSON', 'Happy'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Diwali'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Lolz')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Hindu'), ('PERSON', 'Brown'), ('GPE', 'Hindustan'), ('PERSON', 'Hinduism'), ('GPE', 'Hindus'), ('GPE', 'British'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim'), ('GPE', 'Sahib')]
[('GPE', 'Good')]
[('PERSON', 'Mitra'), ('PERSON', 'Kolkata'), ('PERSON', 'Bengal'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Bangladesh'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Lahore'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'JPASSOCIATE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TIME'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BUY'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'POSITIONAL'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FOR')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RTI')]
[('PERSON', 'Bill'), ('GPE', 'Dramebaaj')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Tata'), ('PERSON', 'Anuj')]
[('PERSON', 'Assam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Meghalaya'), ('GPE', 'Nagaland')]
[('GPE', 'Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Pain'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Real Gain')]
[('PERSON', 'Katil'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Afzhal Guru'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Hell'), ('PERSON', 'Katenge'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JNU'), ('PERSON', 'Bharat')]
[('GPE', 'Unebeivable'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Wrong')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NPA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Bank'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PSU Banks')]
[('GPE', 'Plz'), ('GPE', 'Bought')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Israel')]
[('PERSON', 'Tollywood'), ('PERSON', 'Graphics Cartoon Movie'), ('PERSON', 'Salman'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Compare'), ('PERSON', 'Aamir'), ('PERSON', 'Cinema Bollywood Movies Khan'), ('PERSON', 'Parbhas Acting'), ('GPE', 'Bahubali'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Parbhas Die Heart Fans'), ('PERSON', 'Shahrukh Acting')]
[('GPE', 'Shame'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Pakistani'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LOC'), ('GPE', 'Pak'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'US'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Haram'), ('PERSON', 'Pig Pig'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Harm Dead'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan Pakistan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Scavengers Scavengers'), ('GPE', 'Eat'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Mutilation Mutilation')]
[('GPE', 'Roaming'), ('PERSON', 'Reliance Jio'), ('GPE', 'Airtel'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'STD')]
[('PERSON', 'Tata Counsel'), ('GPE', 'Mistry'), ('PERSON', 'Tata')]
[('PERSON', 'Baba')]
[('GPE', 'Please'), ('PERSON', 'Shameful'), ('GPE', 'Australian')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Mukesh Ambani')]
[('GPE', 'Agreed')]
[('PERSON', 'Amir')]
[('GPE', 'Tweet'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Hate')]
[('PERSON', 'Sitaram Yachur'), ('PERSON', 'Shirish Kunder'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Express'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Justin Bieber'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KoffeeWithKaran'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ENTERTAINMENT'), ('PERSON', 'Karan Johar')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Mohit'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Soni')]
[('GPE', 'Pakisthan')]
[('GPE', 'Kashmiris'), ('PERSON', 'Kashmir'), ('GPE', 'Kashmir'), ('PERSON', 'Email')]
[('GPE', 'British')]
[('GPE', 'Sham')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Dear')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Britishers'), ('GPE', 'Kohima'), ('GPE', 'Japanese'), ('PERSON', 'Mizo'), ('PERSON', 'Pun'), ('PERSON', 'Japs'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FIFA')]
[('PERSON', 'Hero Honda Chowk')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'American'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Orange'), ('PERSON', 'Trump')]
[('GPE', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('LOCATION', 'North East')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Amma')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Total'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Zee'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Zee News')]
[('GPE', 'Irony')]
[('PERSON', 'Tata')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Bihari')]
[('GPE', 'Anuj'), ('GPE', 'Porinju')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MCD')]
[('PERSON', 'Gaurav'), ('PERSON', 'Seth PJ Anshu Mishra Shubham Singh')]
[('PERSON', 'Sorry')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MLA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CM')]
[('GPE', 'North-'), ('GPE', 'China'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Kashmir'), ('PERSON', 'Hyderabad')]
[('GPE', 'Kejriwal'), ('GPE', 'Period')]
[('GPE', 'Hi'), ('GPE', 'True')]
[('GPE', 'Welspun'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GATI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'REC'), ('PERSON', 'Wockhardt'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Metalyst')]
[('GPE', 'True')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'OBCs'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Supreme Court')]
[('PERSON', 'Tata')]
[('GPE', 'Assam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Sanatana Dharma'), ('PERSON', 'God')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims')]
[('GPE', 'Mouni')]
[('GPE', 'Kejriwal'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Lokpal'), ('PERSON', 'Anna'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Rule'), ('GPE', 'High')]
[('PERSON', 'Mohammad'), ('PERSON', 'Partition'), ('GPE', 'Usman'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ALL')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'iPhone')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'TATA')]
[('GPE', 'Hello')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PHILLAURI')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NPA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Bank'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PSU Banks')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('GPE', 'Hope')]
[('PERSON', 'Correption')]
[('GPE', 'Bhaiya'), ('GPE', 'Note'), ('PERSON', 'Patrol')]
[('PERSON', 'Except'), ('GPE', 'Please'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Modiji')]
[('GPE', 'Funny'), ('GPE', 'Christian')]
[('GPE', 'Modi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MCD')]
[('GPE', 'Chelsea')]
[('GPE', 'Bhai'), ('PERSON', 'Mira Rajput')]
[('GPE', 'Pm')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Enfield'), ('PERSON', 'Royal')]
[('PERSON', 'Brexit'), ('GPE', 'Bank'), ('GPE', 'England')]
[('GPE', 'Claim'), ('PERSON', 'Bhakts'), ('PERSON', 'Shame'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GauRakshaks'), ('PERSON', 'Gaumata'), ('GPE', 'Export')]
[('GPE', 'Pappu')]
[('PERSON', 'Fatwa'), ('PERSON', 'Nahid Afreen'), ('GPE', 'Indian Express'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fatwa')]
[('GPE', 'Heheheh'), ('GPE', 'China'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CPEC'), ('GPE', 'Pakistani')]
[('PERSON', 'Hatred'), ('PERSON', 'Daddy'), ('PERSON', 'Matt'), ('PERSON', 'Death')]
[('PERSON', 'Ram'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NATH'), ('PERSON', 'Goenka')]
[('PERSON', 'Mr. Jack')]
[('GPE', 'Haha')]
[('PERSON', 'Army'), ('PERSON', 'Pak'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Heh')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Siva')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'OWNER'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BOT')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SaveIndia'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Long')]
[('PERSON', 'Mr.')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Yechury'), ('PERSON', 'Sitaram'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Marxist')]
[('PERSON', 'Chor Congress'), ('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Effect'), ('PERSON', 'Jio')]
[('GPE', 'Sanghi'), ('PERSON', 'Lokpal'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MCD'), ('PERSON', 'Annaji')]
[('PERSON', 'Icici'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SBI')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SHAMEFUL'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Institute'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JNU')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Lol'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Kashmiris'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BUDGET'), ('GPE', 'Cnbc')]
[('PERSON', 'Shikha Sharma'), ('GPE', 'Fcuk')]
[('PERSON', 'Niccolo'), ('PERSON', 'Plato'), ('PERSON', 'Mr.'), ('PERSON', 'Singh'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Republic')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Sun'), ('GPE', 'Hello')]
[('GPE', 'Tit')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'INC'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FIRST'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MANN')]
[('GPE', 'Sehwag')]
[('PERSON', 'Kashmir'), ('GPE', 'Jammu')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NLI')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('GPE', 'Party'), ('PERSON', 'Tumlogo'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Stupid')]
[('PERSON', 'Hazard'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'Isro')]
[('GPE', 'American'), ('GPE', 'Kuwait')]
[('PERSON', 'Kashmir'), ('GPE', 'Turkey')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP'), ('GPE', 'Perfect'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'POOR'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AANA'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('GPE', 'Vridha')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'HUMANS'), ('PERSON', 'Nobel Prize')]
[('GPE', 'Name')]
[('GPE', 'Single')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Balkrishan Industries'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Sun Pharma')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Gujrat'), ('GPE', 'Muslims'), ('PERSON', 'Mr.')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('GPE', 'Govt'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Dengue'), ('PERSON', 'Kassab')]
[('PERSON', 'Rahul Gandi'), ('GPE', 'Please'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Linux')]
[('PERSON', 'Kashmiri Pandits')]
[('PERSON', 'Nazis')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Shikha Sharma')]
[('GPE', 'Political')]
[('GPE', 'Nonsense')]
[('GPE', 'Revenue')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('PERSON', 'Artifical Intelligence'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Automation')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Sreevalsan'), ('PERSON', 'Vishnu')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ENTERTAINMENT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NiaSharma')]
[('GPE', 'Call')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Bank Branch Manager')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Industrial Hub'), ('GPE', 'South'), ('GPE', 'Need'), ('PERSON', 'Need'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Anti National Elements'), ('PERSON', 'Anti National'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'MODI Ji'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KASHMIR'), ('PERSON', 'Hind S V'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Lobour Acts'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JAMMU'), ('GPE', 'North'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BUSINESS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ISIS')]
[('GPE', 'Sir'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Carry')]
[('GPE', 'Jammu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Line'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Control'), ('GPE', 'Kashmi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LoC'), ('GPE', 'Pakistani'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Tata'), ('GPE', 'Shares')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Kundu'), ('PERSON', 'Anirban')]
[('GPE', 'Jio')]
[('GPE', 'Read')]
[('PERSON', 'Fatwa'), ('PERSON', 'Nahid Afreen'), ('GPE', 'Indian Express'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fatwa')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Hi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MLAs')]
[('GPE', 'Lol'), ('GPE', 'Secure')]
[('PERSON', 'Monthly Budget'), ('GPE', 'Transfer')]
[('PERSON', 'Mukesh Ambani..'), ('PERSON', 'Entrepreneurs')]
[('GPE', 'South'), ('PERSON', 'Q2')]
[('GPE', 'Tum')]
[('GPE', 'Pak'), ('PERSON', 'Jadhav')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'OMG'), ('PERSON', 'Paresh Rawal')]
[('PERSON', 'Adnan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fire'), ('PERSON', 'Usama Ahmad')]
[('GPE', 'Ab'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Abhi'), ('GPE', 'Bus'), ('PERSON', 'Raha')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'QATAR'), ('PERSON', 'Siddu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AIRWAYS')]
[('GPE', 'Ahmedabad')]
[('GPE', 'Lol'), ('PERSON', 'Osama'), ('GPE', 'United'), ('PERSON', 'Malala')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MLA')]
[('PERSON', 'Drona'), ('PERSON', 'Goswami')]
[('GPE', 'Happy')]
[('PERSON', 'True'), ('GPE', 'China')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('GPE', 'Baldy'), ('PERSON', 'Sabha')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'salutetoPM'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'GST'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Plz')]
[('PERSON', 'Kashmir')]
[('PERSON', 'Donald Trump')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RE')]
[('PERSON', 'Media'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'Sonu')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'International'), ('PERSON', 'Naari')]
[('GPE', 'Menakji')]
[('GPE', 'Shame')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Jay'), ('PERSON', 'Hamla Kare Hmari Sena')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'State'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Nation'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'First'), ('GPE', 'Christian'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Catholics'), ('GPE', 'U.S.'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fathers'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Ten Commandments'), ('PERSON', 'James Madison'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'First Amendment'), ('PERSON', 'Doucett'), ('GPE', 'Great'), ('GPE', 'U.S. Almanac'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Black'), ('GPE', 'America'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congressional'), ('GPE', 'Land'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Supreme Law'), ('GPE', 'Church'), ('GPE', 'United States'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Supreme Court'), ('PERSON', 'God')]
[('PERSON', 'Refer'), ('GPE', 'Part'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Facebook')]
[('GPE', 'Useless')]
[('GPE', 'Sounds')]
[('GPE', 'Modi')]
[('GPE', 'Sir'), ('PERSON', 'Irb'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IPO')]
[('PERSON', 'Johar'), ('PERSON', 'Karan')]
[('PERSON', 'Fatwa'), ('PERSON', 'Nahid Afreen'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fatwa')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RS'), ('LOCATION', 'West')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MLA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IPS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'lPS')]
[('GPE', 'Bank')]
[('GPE', 'Kejriwal'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UPA'), ('GSP', 'Anna')]
[('PERSON', 'Well')]
[('GPE', 'Language')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'STRONG')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Dogs'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NDTV'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ABOUT')]
[('PERSON', 'Kerala'), ('GPE', 'Kerala'), ('PERSON', 'Somalia')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BSF'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LOC'), ('PERSON', 'Flag'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UP Election'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Evil'), ('PERSON', 'Unarmed Kashmiris'), ('GPE', 'Pakistani'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Drama'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Kashmiri Militants')]
[('PERSON', 'Singh'), ('GPE', 'Gi'), ('GPE', 'Work'), ('PERSON', 'Satnam')]
[('GPE', 'Hope'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Fool')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NDTV'), ('PERSON', 'Female Actor Kajol Enjoying Beef'), ('PERSON', 'Bollywood')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Pak'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MUSLIMS'), ('PERSON', 'Bajrang'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MUSLIM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ANTI'), ('GPE', 'iNdian'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BABREE')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('PERSON', 'Pawan Goenka'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BS3')]
[('PERSON', 'Mr.')]
[('PERSON', 'Jehadist Scoundrels'), ('PERSON', 'Ashin'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Jose Chellamthara'), ('GSP', 'Goonda')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LIC'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ITR')]
[('GPE', 'Perfect')]
[('GPE', 'Pak'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LOC')]
[('PERSON', 'Infosys Chairman'), ('PERSON', 'Rajiv Bansal'), ('GPE', 'Found')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'FREEDOM')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'REST'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'OWNED'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'STATE'), ('GPE', 'First'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CRORES'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CATCH'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'WORLD'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CONTROL'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BANK'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CORRUPT')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindus'), ('GPE', 'Hindus'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('GPE', 'Koran'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('GPE', 'Sonu')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS')]
[('PERSON', 'Mr. Eric'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Azaan')]
[('PERSON', 'Neel Patel'), ('PERSON', 'Stay')]
[('GPE', 'China'), ('PERSON', 'Xi Jinping')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Delhi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MCD')]
[('PERSON', 'Person')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI')]
[('PERSON', 'Sonu')]
[('GPE', 'Please'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AC'), ('GPE', 'Life')]
[('GPE', 'Brute')]
[('PERSON', 'Punj Lloyd')]
[('GPE', 'Tsk'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'WRONG'), ('PERSON', 'Misha')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('PERSON', 'Pakistani Armed'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Pathankot'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Karachi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'INFIBEAM')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SUE'), ('GPE', 'Idiots'), ('PERSON', 'Modiji')]
[('PERSON', 'Devendra Singh')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Modi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Sheep'), ('GPE', 'Keeps'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Center'), ('GPE', 'Delhi'), ('GPE', 'Wolf'), ('GPE', 'Hypocrite'), ('PERSON', 'Kejriwal'), ('GPE', 'Punjab'), ('PERSON', 'Lokpal')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslim')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Scrap'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LOC Ceasefire')]
[('GPE', 'Bjp')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('GPE', 'Reservation'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'OBCs'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Supreme Court')]
[('PERSON', 'Srk')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Beef'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP Talks')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'DESERVE')]
[('GPE', 'Ye')]
[('PERSON', 'Modiji')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BBTC'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KICL')]
[('PERSON', 'Naxalites')]
[('PERSON', 'Peter School'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THRAI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Convent Schools')]
[('PERSON', 'Zaheer Khan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('PERSON', 'Aishwarya'), ('PERSON', 'Hari Haran')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'IPS'), ('GPE', 'Stand')]
[('GPE', 'Saumya'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Jain')]
[('PERSON', 'Jai Ho')]
[('GPE', 'Kerela')]
[('GPE', 'Ban')]
[('GPE', 'Ban')]
[('GPE', 'Gujrat')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Kim Jong-un'), ('PERSON', 'Heard'), ('PERSON', 'Joseph Stallion'), ('PERSON', 'Adolf Hitler')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PERFORM'), ('PERSON', 'Kiran K')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('GPE', 'Election')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('GPE', 'Rajamouli')]
[('GPE', 'South Africa'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Gupta')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Bajaj'), ('PERSON', 'Bajaj Finserv'), ('PERSON', 'Sanjiv'), ('GPE', 'Bajaj')]
[('GPE', 'Anuj')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Sun Pharma')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI'), ('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('PERSON', 'Vinod'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Gupta')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Islamic')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NRI'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Bhajan')]
[('PERSON', 'Gorakhpur')]
[('GPE', 'Pak'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KURDISTAN'), ('GPE', 'Brutal'), ('PERSON', 'Kashmir'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('GPE', 'Turkey'), ('GPE', 'Turkey Army'), ('GPE', 'Erdogan')]
[('GPE', 'Jain')]
[('PERSON', 'Kapil')]
[('GPE', 'Barbarism')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'IE')]
[('GPE', 'Pak'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LOC')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Hindu'), ('PERSON', 'Anti')]
[('PERSON', 'Refer'), ('GPE', 'Part'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Facebook')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Dude')]
[('GPE', 'Uncle'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Enfield')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindus'), ('PERSON', 'Babur'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Mongol')]
[('GPE', 'Hi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'STRONG'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'STUPID'), ('GPE', 'INDIA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IMMATURE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ACT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DUFFER'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TOFFEES'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BALOONS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RAHUL'), ('GPE', 'CHILDISH')]
[('PERSON', 'Fuckstain')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'OWNER'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BOT')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Pistols'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Abrar')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Jains'), ('PERSON', 'Sikhs'), ('GPE', 'Buddhist'), ('PERSON', 'Jew'), ('PERSON', 'Hindus')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LESSONS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LEARN')]
[('GPE', 'Railway'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Parliament')]
[('GPE', 'Best'), ('GPE', 'Binami')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MP')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'YOU'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THANK')]
[('GPE', 'Election')]
[('GPE', 'NDTV'), ('GPE', 'Stop'), ('PERSON', 'Dear')]
[('GPE', 'Leather'), ('GPE', 'Army'), ('GPE', 'Kasmiri'), ('PERSON', 'Pakistani'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Cow Vegilence')]
[('GPE', 'Canadian'), ('PERSON', 'Swachch Bharat PR')]
[('GPE', 'Shame'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Parties'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Black Money'), ('GPE', 'Political')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'USA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IIT'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('GPE', 'Source'), ('GPE', 'IITs'), ('GPE', 'Narayanamurthy'), ('GPE', 'Kejriwal')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'Smooth'), ('GPE', 'Credit'), ('GPE', 'Mechanism'), ('GPE', 'Fiscal'), ('GPE', 'Regulate')]
[('GPE', 'Kargil'), ('PERSON', 'Mizz Gurmeher')]
[('GPE', 'Bhopalistan'), ('GPE', 'Dravidistan'), ('PERSON', 'Kashmir'), ('GPE', 'Nizamistan')]
[('GPE', 'Bhai'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslims')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('GPE', 'Appeal')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan Army'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Sir')]
[('PERSON', 'Taneja'), ('PERSON', 'Anurag')]
[('GPE', 'Long')]
[('GPE', 'Sir'), ('GPE', 'China')]
[('PERSON', 'Adityanath'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SO Cute'), ('PERSON', 'Cool'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CM')]
[('PERSON', 'Rajnath Singh')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'FII')]
[('GPE', 'Are'), ('PERSON', 'Okk'), ('PERSON', 'Rakesh Shah')]
[('PERSON', 'Delhi')]
[('GPE', 'North')]
[('PERSON', 'God')]
[('GPE', 'Please')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'USA'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Bhelupur')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'US'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Nordic'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NATO'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CAPITALIST')]
[('PERSON', 'History'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NAMO')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'OWNER'), ('PERSON', 'Xingh Kannu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BOT')]
[('GPE', 'Send')]
[('GPE', 'Australia'), ('PERSON', 'Mann')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Election Anna'), ('PERSON', 'Arvinth'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ABP Neaws')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ABP'), ('PERSON', 'Lol')]
[('GPE', 'Thats')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ISIS')]
[('PERSON', 'Which'), ('GPE', 'Wait')]
[('PERSON', 'Ala')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'GDP')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Mukesh Ambani')]
[('PERSON', 'Loan'), ('GPE', 'Poor'), ('PERSON', 'Rich')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Chandigarh'), ('PERSON', 'Top Hizbul Militant'), ('GPE', 'Kashmiri'), ('PERSON', 'Zakir'), ('PERSON', 'Musa')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Had'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Union Budget'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DEMONETIZATION')]
[('GPE', 'Google'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Microsoft')]
[('PERSON', 'Arab')]
[('PERSON', 'Fatwa'), ('PERSON', 'Nahid Afreen'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fatwa')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Mumbai'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Shiv Sena'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Mumbai'), ('GPE', 'Philly'), ('GSP', 'Philadelphia')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MD')]
[('GPE', 'Dear')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RTI')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Enough')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Rahul')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Sikh')]
[('GPE', 'Hindus')]
[('PERSON', 'Kiran Bedi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Kapil Mishra'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CM')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Advocate Meritocracy'), ('PERSON', 'Gandhis')]
[('PERSON', 'Amin Patel')]
[('PERSON', 'Nawaz'), ('PERSON', 'Jindal')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Superb')]
[('PERSON', 'Rohit'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TRP')]
[('GPE', 'Express')]
[('GPE', 'Agreed')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims')]
[('GPE', 'Hello')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Defence'), ('PERSON', 'Narendra Modi India'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Jawarlal'), ('PERSON', 'Occupied Kashmir'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UN'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('PERSON', 'Nehru')]
[('GPE', 'U.S.'), ('PERSON', 'David'), ('PERSON', 'Clark')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('GPE', 'Yup'), ('GPE', 'Hindus')]
[('GPE', 'God'), ('PERSON', 'Noel Cyril Lazaro')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Naik'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IRF'), ('PERSON', 'Zakir')]
[('GPE', 'Wt'), ('GPE', 'Same')]
[('GPE', 'Media'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'HDFC Bank')]
[('GPE', 'Woman')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Eng')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SIBALM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JAURAM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FARCE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ETC'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DISGRACE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SLAVES'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ILLITERATE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ROBOTS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NOISE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SASI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CALL'), ('GPE', 'CHIDU'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SUDDENLY'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'WHITE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DRIVING'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DOLLARS FOR')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Srivastava'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MEERA'), ('PERSON', 'Surbhi')]
[('PERSON', 'Seems')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CRAP'), ('PERSON', 'Rapist'), ('PERSON', 'Harmon')]
[('PERSON', 'Ratio')]
[('GPE', 'Karan')]
[('PERSON', 'Cows'), ('PERSON', 'People')]
[('GPE', 'Fahad')]
[('GPE', 'Talk')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Gujarati')]
[('PERSON', 'Manisha Gupta'), ('PERSON', 'Awesome')]
[('GPE', 'Kashmir')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Kerala')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Chinese'), ('GPE', 'Shameful')]
[('GPE', 'Great'), ('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('PERSON', 'Zabardast Mindblowing Wonderfull'), ('PERSON', 'Nawab'), ('PERSON', 'Superrrrrrrrrrrrr Duperrrrrrrrr Awesome Fantastic Fabulous Excellent'), ('PERSON', 'Nihal Very'), ('PERSON', 'Zabardast Mindblowing Wonderfull Best')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Amit Shah'), ('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('GPE', 'Hi'), ('PERSON', 'Stop'), ('GPE', 'Public')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Thomas'), ('PERSON', 'Kuruvilla Baven')]
[('PERSON', 'Alert')]
[('PERSON', 'Rajas'), ('GPE', 'Nawabs'), ('PERSON', 'Supreme'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GSP', 'Constitution')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MKT')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Farah')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'FII'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FM')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'India Modiji')]
[('PERSON', 'Indian Overseas Bank'), ('PERSON', 'Bought')]
[('GSP', 'Russia'), ('GPE', 'China'), ('GPE', 'Hound'), ('GPE', 'Monger'), ('GPE', 'Trump'), ('GPE', 'Asia'), ('PERSON', 'Bomb'), ('GSP', 'Syria')]
[('GPE', 'Hell')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'Stupid')]
[('GPE', 'Modi'), ('PERSON', 'Feku')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'EVM'), ('GPE', 'Voice')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('PERSON', 'Sri Ratan Tata'), ('GPE', 'Nobody')]
[('GPE', 'Fake')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RIP')]
[('GPE', 'Superb')]
[('GPE', 'Har')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'WarOnBlackMoney')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Turkey')]
[('GPE', 'Fake')]
[('GPE', 'Man')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP'), ('GPE', 'Shame'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TRP')]
[('GPE', 'Fake')]
[('GPE', 'Again'), ('GPE', 'Modijee'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('PERSON', 'Modijee')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Good')]
[('GPE', 'Fudu')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NEWSCHANAL')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Semitic')]
[('PERSON', 'Nupur'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Prakash This')]
[('GPE', 'Umnn')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Happiness'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Citizens'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ALL')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AIMIM')]
[('GPE', 'Goa')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Pak'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Naxals'), ('GPE', 'Naxal')]
[('GPE', 'Problem')]
[('GPE', 'Gr8')]
[('GPE', 'Indians'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Indonesia'), ('GPE', 'Chinese'), ('GPE', 'Medan'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJp')]
[('GPE', 'Chetan'), ('PERSON', 'Baan'), ('PERSON', 'Bhagat'), ('PERSON', 'Arjun'), ('PERSON', 'Whereas'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Tulsi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Mayawati')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Supreme Court'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NGO')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Idiot')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'UPA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Mahatma'), ('PERSON', 'Sanghi'), ('GPE', 'Sanghi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AK'), ('PERSON', 'Lokpal')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ROYAL'), ('GPE', 'Shld')]
[('GPE', 'Japan'), ('GSP', 'US'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Hong Kong')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Appreciate'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CNBC'), ('GPE', 'Sonia'), ('GPE', 'Nice')]
[('GPE', 'Clean'), ('PERSON', 'Solar')]
[('GPE', 'Touch')]
[('GPE', 'Love')]
[('GPE', 'Gd')]
[('GPE', 'Bjp')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'YOGI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JAI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FUTURE')]
[('PERSON', 'Rahul')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DELHI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ALSO'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'INCLUDE')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CPI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JDU'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UP')]
[('GPE', 'Dont')]
[('GPE', 'Google')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Kerala')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ICJ'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'TLDR')]
[('PERSON', 'License'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RTO')]
[('PERSON', 'Tata')]
[('GPE', 'Country')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'JanDhan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Note'), ('PERSON', 'Note Ban'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UBI'), ('PERSON', 'Col Lamba')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'JNU')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('PERSON', 'Ambani'), ('GPE', 'MadamG')]
[('PERSON', 'Sorry')]
[('PERSON', 'Akhtar'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Miya')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MLAs')]
[('GPE', 'Stop'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Discussing'), ('PERSON', 'Stop')]
[('PERSON', 'Lokpal Bill'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Phadanavis'), ('GPE', 'Uddhav')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Jhundsutta'), ('PERSON', 'Rumour'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Express'), ('PERSON', 'Afwhaa Times'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Defence'), ('GPE', 'China')]
[('PERSON', 'Razi'), ('PERSON', 'Ashraf Just')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BSP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LoC'), ('GPE', 'Lakh'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('GPE', 'Pakistani')]
[('GPE', 'Fascist')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Sitharam'), ('PERSON', 'Iam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JNU')]
[('GPE', 'Vivaram')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Markets'), ('GPE', 'Global'), ('PERSON', 'Nifty'), ('PERSON', 'Trump')]
[('GPE', 'Tired')]
[('GPE', 'Brigade'), ('GPE', 'Good')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('PERSON', 'Azaan'), ('GPE', 'Azan'), ('PERSON', 'Ganpati'), ('PERSON', 'Sonu')]
[('GPE', 'Lol')]
[('PERSON', 'Kejriwal')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('PERSON', 'Menaka Gandhi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DOGS'), ('PERSON', 'Madom')]
[('GPE', 'Great'), ('GPE', 'Many')]
[('PERSON', 'Carry')]
[('GPE', 'Nice')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SP')]
[('GPE', 'Jain'), ('PERSON', 'Anmol')]
[('PERSON', 'Done'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Prince Fadii'), ('GPE', 'April'), ('PERSON', 'Auto Comment')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Cashless')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('PERSON', 'Alkhyda'), ('GPE', 'Which'), ('PERSON', 'Bala Maoists'), ('PERSON', 'Christian'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IRA'), ('PERSON', 'Hindus'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LRA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim'), ('GPE', 'Isis')]
[('GPE', 'Ramdev')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Hafiz'), ('PERSON', 'Saeed')]
[('PERSON', 'Itchguard')]
[('PERSON', 'Karan'), ('GPE', 'Mediocracy')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'US')]
[('PERSON', 'Sonu Nigam')]
[('PERSON', 'Shashi Taroor'), ('GPE', 'Make'), ('PERSON', 'Modiji'), ('PERSON', 'Mr.')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ICICI Bank'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Private'), ('GPE', 'Way'), ('GPE', 'True'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Digital India')]
[('PERSON', 'Dmart'), ('GPE', 'Sonia')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'HELL')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindu')]
[('PERSON', 'Arvind')]
[('GPE', 'Kerala')]
[('PERSON', 'Sayed'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Talak'), ('GPE', 'America')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LG')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SRK'), ('PERSON', 'Shirish Kunder')]
[('GPE', 'Reason')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Tina')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'THE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'REAL'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THANKS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BARINDER FOR')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RRB')]
[('PERSON', 'Vasa'), ('PERSON', 'Madhukar Never'), ('GPE', 'Gujarat')]
[('GPE', 'Burnol')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Hinduism'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Secularism')]
[('PERSON', 'Subhash')]
[('PERSON', 'Karan Johar'), ('PERSON', 'Kangana')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Review Petition'), ('PERSON', 'Sick SSI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Board Level'), ('GPE', 'Dubious'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Law'), ('PERSON', 'Deepika'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'State'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Choicest Blessings'), ('PERSON', 'Sir'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Commissions'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SBI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Industries Department'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Consumer Court'), ('PERSON', 'Quasi Judicial'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Hindu'), ('GPE', 'Kannur'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Medical College Trivandrum'), ('GPE', 'Email'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'National'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Kerala'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'City Hospital Mangalore'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SSI'), ('PERSON', 'Revenue Recovery Act'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Commission'), ('PERSON', 'Malayalam Manorama'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CDRC'), ('PERSON', 'Elembilayi Sadanandan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ISI'), ('PERSON', 'Kannur District Hospital'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Vengeful'), ('GPE', 'Entrepreneur'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CDRCs'), ('PERSON', 'Human Rights Commissions'), ('PERSON', 'Trivandrum'), ('GPE', 'Civil'), ('GPE', 'Crutches'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'OTS'), ('PERSON', 'Non Judicial Officers'), ('PERSON', 'Kerala State Consumer Disputes Redressal'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KFC'), ('FACILITY', 'Head Office'), ('PERSON', 'Crutches'), ('PERSON', 'Deccan Chronicle'), ('PERSON', 'Vishnu Nilayam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Central And State'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Palauan'), ('PERSON', 'Kerala State'), ('GPE', 'New'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LIMITATION Act'), ('GPE', 'Chovva'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Corrupted')]
[('PERSON', 'Good'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Cont')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'FZ')]
[('GPE', 'Laws'), ('GPE', 'Triple'), ('PERSON', 'Zakia Jafri')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindu'), ('GPE', 'Hindu'), ('PERSON', 'Azaan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Somu Nigam'), ('PERSON', 'Bhajan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Bank Nifty'), ('GPE', 'Market'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Divident')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI'), ('GPE', 'Hopefully'), ('GPE', 'Hello')]
[('GPE', 'Jaitley'), ('GPE', 'Rubbish'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'OWNER'), ('PERSON', 'Xingh Kannu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BOT')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('PERSON', 'Coal India'), ('PERSON', 'Anuj'), ('GPE', 'Hii')]
[('GPE', 'Biwi')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'China'), ('GPE', 'Chinese'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Reservation')]
[('GPE', 'Shame'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AIFF')]
[('GPE', 'Patel'), ('GPE', 'Economic'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CRR'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Patel'), ('PERSON', 'Mr.'), ('PERSON', 'Sir')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS')]
[('PERSON', 'School Employee')]
[('PERSON', 'Kumar Kumar'), ('PERSON', 'Sundar')]
[('GPE', 'Dont')]
[('GPE', 'Please'), ('GPE', 'SJ'), ('PERSON', 'Dear')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MCD'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PVR'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'H1B'), ('GPE', 'Capital'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Boeing'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Natak Raja'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CBI'), ('PERSON', 'Dawood')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Dubai'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ISI')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MEDIA'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Indians'), ('GPE', 'Film')]
[('GPE', 'Set')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KP'), ('GPE', 'China')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Shame')]
[('GPE', 'Mumbai'), ('GPE', 'Wow'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Express'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BMC'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Kashmir')]
[('GPE', 'Saudi Arabia')]
[('GPE', 'Mentaly')]
[('GPE', 'Shame')]
[('GPE', 'Singapore'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PM')]
[('PERSON', 'Muscat'), ('GPE', 'Good')]
[('GPE', 'Army'), ('GPE', 'Kashmir'), ('PERSON', 'Moist')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'EXPLANATION Ie'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'WHY'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'HUGE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CONFIDENCE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THE SOURCE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CASE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'VAILD'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NOT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PROPER'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'REASONS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SUDDEN')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'WB'), ('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Khali')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Black'), ('PERSON', 'Soren Kierkegaard'), ('PERSON', 'Doucett')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'IPO')]
[('GPE', 'Guys')]
[('PERSON', 'Sahyad Us'), ('PERSON', 'Aur'), ('GPE', 'Talak'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Bina')]
[('GPE', 'Vague'), ('PERSON', 'Saffron')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'TRAI')]
[('PERSON', 'Sir Ji'), ('GPE', 'Ladla'), ('PERSON', 'Support Namo')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('PERSON', 'Singh'), ('GPE', 'Goa')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'APP')]
[('GPE', 'Change')]
[('GPE', 'Sonam')]
[('GPE', 'Loudspeaker'), ('PERSON', 'Islam'), ('GPE', 'Azaan')]
[('PERSON', 'Kunal'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Gawri')]
[('GPE', 'Wipro'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'QoQ')]
[('GPE', 'Decision')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FAMILIES'), ('PERSON', 'Did'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ALCOHOL')]
[('PERSON', 'Vishwa Yandigeri'), ('PERSON', 'Dear')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Communism'), ('GPE', 'RUBBISH'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Communist'), ('LOCATION', 'West Bengal')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JNU')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NDA')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Havell'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DHFL')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CNBC'), ('PERSON', 'Happy Navratri'), ('PERSON', 'Anuj')]
[('PERSON', 'Moron')]
[('PERSON', 'Rolta')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Bjp'), ('PERSON', 'Anna'), ('PERSON', 'Lok')]
[('PERSON', 'Rip')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Bajaj'), ('PERSON', 'Guys'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LOVE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SIR')]
[('GPE', 'Benami')]
[('PERSON', 'Nawas Shariff'), ('GPE', 'Lahore'), ('PERSON', 'Sorry')]
[('GPE', 'Birla')]
[('GPE', 'Whom')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistani')]
[('GPE', 'Beef'), ('GPE', 'Hinduism'), ('GPE', 'Rigveda'), ('PERSON', 'Vashistha Dharmasutra'), ('PERSON', 'Brahma'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Cow Mata'), ('PERSON', 'Indra'), ('GPE', 'Shatpath Brahmin'), ('GPE', 'Cow'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Brahmin')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Hope')]
[('PERSON', 'Arabi Muslims'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JNU')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'HCC')]
[('PERSON', 'Will')]
[('PERSON', 'Fatwa'), ('PERSON', 'Nahid Afreen'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fatwa')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'DANGER'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'REAL'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SUPPORT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THEY')]
[('GPE', 'Nbcc')]
[('GPE', 'INDIAN'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BELOW')]
[('PERSON', 'Freedom Fighters')]
[('GPE', 'Maulana'), ('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('GPE', 'Muslims')]
[('GPE', 'Average')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CLEAN'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AMERICA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'INDIA')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Indians'), ('GPE', 'Experts')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'YOUR'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'WHEN'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MEAN')]
[('PERSON', 'Amit Shah'), ('PERSON', 'Rajnath Singh')]
[('GPE', 'Humanity'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Democratic')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'WIPRO'), ('PERSON', 'Infy'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TCS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'INFY'), ('GPE', 'Market')]
[('PERSON', 'Rahul Pagariya')]
[('GPE', 'Please'), ('PERSON', 'Simply')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Justice Appeal'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BLACK'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SOMETHING'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MEDIA Please')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'KRK'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Kejarival'), ('PERSON', 'Mr.')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CNBC')]
[('GPE', 'Omjay'), ('PERSON', 'Devi Merry Mata'), ('PERSON', 'Jay Mata'), ('PERSON', 'Job')]
[('GPE', 'Dont')]
[('PERSON', 'Vijayan')]
[('GPE', 'Govt'), ('PERSON', 'Pradesh'), ('PERSON', 'Eat Up Patient'), ('PERSON', 'Madhya'), ('GPE', 'Hospital')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Islam')]
[('GPE', 'Kabhi')]
[('GPE', 'Hope'), ('PERSON', 'Dawood')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Central')]
[('GPE', 'Body'), ('GPE', 'Engine'), ('PERSON', 'Royal Enfield')]
[('GPE', 'America'), ('GPE', 'Indians')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'DeMo')]
[('GPE', 'Care')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Vrinda')]
[('PERSON', 'Discuss'), ('PERSON', 'Delhi'), ('GPE', 'Revenge')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Kerala')]
[('GPE', 'Israel')]
[('PERSON', 'Niraj')]
[('PERSON', 'Hard')]
[('PERSON', 'Marathon'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Marathon')]
[('GPE', 'Khaki'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'HRD'), ('GPE', 'Irani'), ('PERSON', 'Delhi')]
[('GPE', 'Govt')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress Debar'), ('GPE', 'Mallikaarjun')]
[('PERSON', 'Lenin')]
[('PERSON', 'Singh'), ('GPE', 'Budget')]
[('GPE', 'Problem'), ('PERSON', 'Amir'), ('GPE', 'Nobody')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SUFFERING'), ('GPE', 'Suffer'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Spot')]
[('GPE', 'New')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('PERSON', 'Nirmalya')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Hasidic'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Zionist'), ('GPE', 'Israel')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'DFR'), ('GPE', 'Band'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RAISE')]
[('GPE', 'Ufff')]
[('GPE', 'Rule'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IMA')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Harvard')]
[('GPE', 'Fake')]
[('PERSON', 'Same'), ('PERSON', 'Pakistani')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CPM')]
[('PERSON', 'Bollywood')]
[('PERSON', 'Sharad Power')]
[('PERSON', 'Asrar Ul Haq')]
[('PERSON', 'Killer Ram'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Nathu'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Gandhi')]
[('GPE', 'Gud')]
[('GPE', 'Andhra'), ('PERSON', 'Babu Naidu')]
[('PERSON', 'Ishaq Zada'), ('GPE', 'May'), ('PERSON', 'Auto Comment')]
[('GPE', 'Swiss')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Focus'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Unemployment'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MOBS')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PERFECT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CONGRESS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CHANGE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BIGARE')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Pak')]
[('GPE', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Nope')]
[('GPE', 'Sunny')]
[('GPE', 'Disgusting')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'WIFE'), ('PERSON', 'Sorry')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Reserve Bank'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Religion'), ('GPE', 'Europe'), ('PERSON', 'Azan'), ('GPE', 'Pray')]
[('PERSON', 'Abhijeet'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Ravi Yechuri')]
[('GPE', 'Bheem')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PYTHONS'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'krO India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SIT3'), ('GPE', 'May'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'clOse'), ('PERSON', 'Waqas Ali')]
[('GPE', 'Sir'), ('GPE', 'Delhi'), ('PERSON', 'Law')]
[('GPE', 'Gon')]
[('GPE', 'Tata')]
[('GPE', 'Are')]
[('PERSON', 'Bharat'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Financial'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LT Finance'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Finance')]
[('GPE', 'Forget'), ('GPE', 'Freedom'), ('GPE', 'Lahore'), ('PERSON', 'Sukhdev'), ('PERSON', 'Rajguru'), ('PERSON', 'Bhagat Singh')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Chemical Ali')]
[('PERSON', 'Fatwa'), ('PERSON', 'Nahid Afreen'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fatwa')]
[('PERSON', 'Rajiv Gandhi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AB Vajpai'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PV Narsimha Rao'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'OWNER'), ('PERSON', 'Xingh Kannu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BOT')]
[('GPE', 'Sir')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NPAs'), ('PERSON', 'Arundhati Bhattacharya')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Indians'), ('PERSON', 'Modijee')]
[('GPE', 'Pity')]
[('PERSON', 'Bihar'), ('GPE', 'Perfect')]
[('PERSON', 'Yedurappa'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CNG'), ('GPE', 'Electricity'), ('PERSON', 'Swaraj'), ('GPE', 'Funds'), ('PERSON', 'Mulayam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JanLokpal'), ('PERSON', 'Mayawati'), ('PERSON', 'Water'), ('GPE', 'Politics'), ('PERSON', 'Rahul'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('GPE', 'Difference'), ('PERSON', 'Petrol')]
[('GPE', 'European'), ('PERSON', 'Rahul'), ('PERSON', 'Rohit')]
[('PERSON', 'Coal'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CWG')]
[('PERSON', 'Jayant Sinha')]
[('PERSON', 'Hebrew'), ('GPE', 'American'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NATIONAL'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ENGLISH'), ('GPE', 'Israel'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NATIONAL Launguage')]
[('GPE', 'Courtesy'), ('PERSON', 'Dwivedi'), ('PERSON', 'Chandra')]
[('GPE', 'Bjp')]
[('GPE', 'Courageous'), ('PERSON', 'Cho'), ('GPE', 'Took'), ('GPE', 'Admired'), ('GPE', 'Straight')]
[('GPE', 'US'), ('GSP', 'US'), ('GPE', 'Iraq'), ('PERSON', 'Alqeda'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'US'), ('GPE', 'Afghanistan'), ('GPE', 'Israel'), ('PERSON', 'Trump'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'USSR'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Taliban')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('PERSON', 'Sachin'), ('GPE', 'Hyderabad')]
[('GPE', 'Delhi'), ('PERSON', 'Delhi')]
[('GPE', 'Jokistan')]
[('GPE', 'Jai'), ('GPE', 'Thanks'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Canada')]
[('GPE', 'Porki'), ('GPE', 'Porkis'), ('GPE', 'Porkistan')]
[('GPE', 'America')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'HyDer'), ('PERSON', 'Khoso Pakistan')]
[('PERSON', 'Supreme Commander'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JNU'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Maoist Council')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Bjp'), ('PERSON', 'Anna'), ('PERSON', 'Lok')]
[('GPE', 'Ab')]
[('GPE', 'INDIA')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'TOAL Department'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NAP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('PERSON', 'Modiji')]
[('PERSON', 'Aap')]
[('PERSON', 'Vasa')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Available Veg Tobacco'), ('GPE', 'Menu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Buffalo'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Free Home Delivery'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Veg Beef'), ('GPE', 'New'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Available'), ('GPE', 'Vegetarian'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Available Veg Fish'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Available Veg Egg'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Available Veg Whiskey'), ('GPE', 'Enjoy'), ('PERSON', 'Uttar Pradesh Restaurant'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Available Veg Mutton'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Mode Cheers'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Available Veg Chicken')]
[('PERSON', 'Infy TCS')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'Anuj')]
[('GPE', 'Fear')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NOW'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Hindus'), ('GPE', 'Kashmiris'), ('PERSON', 'Kashmir'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim'), ('GPE', 'Sub'), ('PERSON', 'Email')]
[('GPE', 'Ur')]
[('GPE', 'Fake')]
[('GPE', 'Annaji')]
[('GPE', 'INDIAN'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ARMY')]
[('GPE', 'Rs')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Terrorist')]
[('GPE', 'Bakwaas')]
[('GPE', 'Americans')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'USA'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Sachin')]
[('GPE', 'Tradition')]
[('GPE', 'Modi')]
[('GPE', 'Respect')]
[('GPE', 'Hello')]
[('GPE', 'Iam')]
[('GPE', 'Which'), ('GPE', 'Wo'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UK'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Digital'), ('GPE', 'Dream'), ('PERSON', 'Modi Ji'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NDA')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CONCUR'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Diwan Comments'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Logistic Stock'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Container Corporation'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Navratna Company'), ('PERSON', 'Prakash')]
[('PERSON', 'Frank'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Ezung')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LOC'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Indians'), ('PERSON', 'Soon')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RRS')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Demonetization')]
[('GPE', 'Money'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Modi Ji')]
[('GPE', 'Modi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BAT')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'UP')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Sitaram'), ('PERSON', 'Shame'), ('GPE', 'Cpim')]
[('GPE', 'China'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Civilian'), ('PERSON', 'Gandhi'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Jallikattu Train'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UnitedNation Pl Help')]
[('GPE', 'Sad')]
[('PERSON', 'Sonu Nigam')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Aizawl Fc'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Majority')]
[('GPE', 'Shame'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Benjamin Rush'), ('PERSON', 'Puerto Rico'), ('PERSON', 'Margaux'), ('PERSON', 'Arabic'), ('GPE', 'Israel'), ('PERSON', 'Bill'), ('PERSON', 'Adams'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Nation'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Blackguard Paine'), ('PERSON', 'John'), ('GPE', 'U.S.'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Roman Catholic'), ('GPE', 'Indigenous'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Ten Commandments'), ('PERSON', 'James Madison'), ('PERSON', 'Thomas Paine'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Farewell Address'), ('PERSON', 'Christian'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Subjects'), ('GPE', 'English'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Bey'), ('PERSON', 'Treaty'), ('PERSON', 'Statehood'), ('GPE', 'America'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Treaty'), ('GPE', 'Barbary'), ('GPE', 'Christianity'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Article'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'New World'), ('GPE', 'United States'), ('PERSON', 'George Washington'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Tripoli'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Roman Catholic Church'), ('GPE', 'Rights'), ('GPE', 'Independence'), ('GPE', 'Reason'), ('GPE', 'Peace'), ('GPE', 'Christian')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Black'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TN')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI')]
[('GPE', 'Good')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'YouTube')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Brave')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Himalayas')]
[('GPE', 'Psycho')]
[('GPE', 'Shot'), ('GPE', 'Kindly')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'DOMINAR')]
[('PERSON', 'Change'), ('PERSON', 'Kashmir'), ('GPE', 'Ninda'), ('GPE', 'Forces')]
[('PERSON', 'Raj Thackeray'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PM')]
[('GPE', 'Canara')]
[('GPE', 'Swiss'), ('PERSON', 'Tulu'), ('GPE', 'Bhaijan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CM'), ('GPE', 'Modi'), ('PERSON', 'Yogi'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Jamuna Tehzeeb'), ('GPE', 'Indians')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NDTV'), ('PERSON', 'Millions'), ('PERSON', 'Billions')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Govt')]
[('GPE', 'Haha')]
[('GPE', 'Sultan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Assam')]
[('GPE', 'Massive')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JANTA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'HAI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DESH')]
[('GPE', 'Burn')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Honest'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MCD'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Nobody'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('GPE', 'Madam')]
[('PERSON', 'Kumar Sharma'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MODI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('PERSON', 'Deepak')]
[('PERSON', 'Temple')]
[('GPE', 'Please')]
[('GPE', 'Feudalistic'), ('GPE', 'Mamta'), ('GPE', 'Singur')]
[('GPE', 'Sigh')]
[('GPE', 'Bankruptacy'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Responsibility')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'France'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Republic'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UAE')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Hero'), ('GPE', 'Real')]
[('PERSON', 'Audi')]
[('PERSON', 'Happy')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PM Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('GPE', 'Fatwa')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MODI Fan'), ('PERSON', 'Every Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Govt'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Same')]
[('GPE', 'Jansatta'), ('GPE', 'News')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('GSP', 'US'), ('GPE', 'Provide'), ('GPE', 'Muslims')]
[('PERSON', 'Bhuvanesh'), ('PERSON', 'Trivedi Utkarsh Mishra')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Factlble')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PM Modi'), ('GPE', 'Poor'), ('GPE', 'Corruption')]
[('PERSON', 'Sadbhav Engineering'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JAMNA Auto')]
[('PERSON', 'Justin Bieber')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Infrastructure'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MakeInIndia')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('GPE', 'Bangladesh'), ('GPE', 'Iran'), ('PERSON', 'Azan'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Arab')]
[('GSP', 'Clean'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Swiss'), ('GPE', 'Panama')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Hazare'), ('PERSON', 'Arvind Kejriwal'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ISI'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan Army')]
[('PERSON', 'Already'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Hazare')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Secularism')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JANTA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'HAI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DESH')]
[('GPE', 'Modi')]
[('GPE', 'Cashless')]
[('GPE', 'Demonitization')]
[('GPE', 'Infra'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Metro'), ('GPE', 'Time')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Nation'), ('PERSON', 'Block Buster')]
[('GPE', 'Wow')]
[('GPE', 'Sonia')]
[('GPE', 'Nation')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Assam'), ('PERSON', 'Kashmir'), ('GPE', 'Punjab'), ('GPE', 'Nagaland')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'IPS')]
[('GPE', 'Whereas')]
[('GPE', 'Priyanca'), ('GPE', 'Stupid'), ('GPE', 'Sonu'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Amrita Ajitprasad')]
[('GPE', 'Dynamic')]
[('GPE', 'Gujratis')]
[('GPE', 'Hedge')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Mistry'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TATAs'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Ratan Tata')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Vodafone')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI'), ('GPE', 'Demonetisation'), ('GPE', 'Bangalore')]
[('GPE', 'British'), ('GPE', 'Gandhiji')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'OWNER'), ('PERSON', 'Xingh Kannu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BOT')]
[('GPE', 'Indian Body'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan Army'), ('PERSON', 'Strike Surgical Strike Surgical Strike')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Israel')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Techniques'), ('PERSON', 'Swachh Bharat Abhiyaan')]
[('PERSON', 'Saddam'), ('GPE', 'China'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('GPE', 'Superb')]
[('PERSON', 'Dawood CBI'), ('PERSON', 'Aditya Nath')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'INSIDE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FAILURE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ENEMY'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ARMY')]
[('PERSON', 'Sir'), ('GPE', 'Hi'), ('PERSON', 'Expiry')]
[('GPE', 'Poverty'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ONLY'), ('PERSON', 'Tamil Naadu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NEVER'), ('GPE', 'Time')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ToT'), ('PERSON', 'Sundar')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Bjp'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('GPE', 'Hazare')]
[('GPE', 'Show')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CBN'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Shruti')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'coMplain Piyush')]
[('PERSON', 'Kapil Kaul'), ('GPE', 'Current')]
[('GPE', 'Fantastic')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PROUD'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GOOD'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KERALA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FROM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LUCK'), ('PERSON', 'Abhay Singh')]
[('GPE', 'Maharashtra'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Express'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BMC'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Hindus')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'EVM'), ('PERSON', 'Andolan')]
[('GPE', 'Delhi'), ('PERSON', 'Manoj Tiwari')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Beef'), ('GPE', 'Il')]
[('GPE', 'Reservation')]
[('GPE', 'Bahuballi')]
[('GPE', 'Sir')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI'), ('PERSON', 'Doubt')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Gandhiji'), ('PERSON', 'Nehru'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PehlaKadam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LIVE')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'IMA')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Opinion'), ('GPE', 'Hahahaha'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Kid'), ('PERSON', 'Pakistani')]
[('PERSON', 'Raaz')]
[('GPE', 'Nice')]
[('PERSON', 'Bhakts')]
[('PERSON', 'Mukesh Ambani')]
[('GPE', 'Bina')]
[('GPE', 'Saudis'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'INTOLERANT')]
[('PERSON', 'Qamar'), ('GPE', 'Hindu'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Ghauri'), ('PERSON', 'Aghori')]
[('PERSON', 'Azam Khan'), ('GPE', 'Road'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Politician'), ('GPE', 'Please'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('GPE', 'Inconsiderate')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Jio')]
[('PERSON', 'Vacancy'), ('PERSON', 'Kailash Vijayvargiya'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ISI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Tadipaar Shah'), ('GPE', 'New'), ('GPE', 'Candidate'), ('GPE', 'Fekendra')]
[('GPE', 'Russia'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GDP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IMF'), ('PERSON', 'Erdogan'), ('GSP', 'Turkish'), ('GPE', 'EU'), ('GPE', 'Turkish'), ('PERSON', 'Recap Tayyip Erdogan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Turkish Central Bank'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Green Card'), ('PERSON', 'Education'), ('PERSON', 'Inflation'), ('GPE', 'Turkey'), ('PERSON', 'Erdoan')]
[('GPE', 'Headline')]
[('GPE', 'Have')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistani')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ALLAH')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Superb')]
[('GPE', 'Madhubala')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Central Banks'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'European Commission'), ('GPE', 'European'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Inter-American Development Bank'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'International Finance Corporation'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'International Monetary Fund'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'State'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Central Bank'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'United Nations'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'International'), ('GPE', 'New Politic')]
[('GPE', 'Idiot')]
[('PERSON', 'Neil'), ('PERSON', 'Khurana')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP'), ('GPE', 'Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Delhi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Kejriwal'), ('PERSON', 'Anna Hazare'), ('PERSON', 'Kejriwal')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Competition')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CNBC'), ('PERSON', 'Purpose')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Sir'), ('PERSON', 'Suresh')]
[('PERSON', 'Shah')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('GPE', 'AIMIM'), ('PERSON', 'Animals'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Large Heart')]
[('GPE', 'Indin')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Real'), ('GPE', 'Randia')]
[('GPE', 'Sensible')]
[('PERSON', 'Award'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JNU')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('GPE', 'Digvijay')]
[('GPE', 'Fail')]
[('GPE', 'Romeos')]
[('GPE', 'Girish'), ('PERSON', 'Rajani')]
[('GPE', 'Anuj')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Gandhi'), ('GPE', 'Indra'), ('PERSON', 'Rajiv')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Cabinet')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Govt'), ('PERSON', 'Really'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Kangana'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KJOs')]
[('GPE', 'Jayalalitha')]
[('GPE', 'Delhi'), ('PERSON', 'Viswas'), ('PERSON', 'Kumar Vishwas')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ABSOLUTE')]
[('PERSON', 'Amit Shah'), ('GPE', 'Jaitly'), ('PERSON', 'Joshi'), ('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('PERSON', 'Advani')]
[('PERSON', 'Singh'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Shubham'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GDP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CONSUMPTION'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PANI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'HUNGER'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DEPENDS')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BAT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ISPR'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Army'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Krishna Ghatti'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Buttal'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Modi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Service'), ('GPE', 'Food')]
[('GPE', 'Hazare'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Corruption')]
[('PERSON', 'Jumlas'), ('GPE', 'Karnataka'), ('PERSON', 'Chosen Development')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'Pak'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'OMG'), ('PERSON', 'Enfield')]
[('GPE', 'Shahrukh')]
[('GPE', 'Hitler'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Army')]
[('PERSON', 'Nahid'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Ravish'), ('PERSON', 'Evil'), ('GPE', 'Please'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('GPE', 'Islam'), ('PERSON', 'Islam'), ('PERSON', 'Sharia Law'), ('GPE', 'Appeal'), ('PERSON', 'Ndtv')]
[('GPE', 'Delhi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'TATA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AOA')]
[('PERSON', 'Jat'), ('PERSON', 'Patel'), ('PERSON', 'Dalits'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Repeated'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SC'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Sikh'), ('GPE', 'Ghettoisation'), ('GPE', 'Tamil'), ('PERSON', 'Reason'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Dalit'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ST'), ('PERSON', 'Muslim'), ('PERSON', 'Tribal')]
[('GPE', 'Opposition')]
[('PERSON', 'Karey Naa'), ('PERSON', 'Woh')]
[('GPE', 'Hru')]
[('PERSON', 'Tyler'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Brown')]
[('PERSON', 'Tiwari'), ('PERSON', 'Malviya Nagar'), ('PERSON', 'Delhi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SRK'), ('GPE', 'T10')]
[('GPE', 'Cheap')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SayNoToSasikala')]
[('PERSON', 'Which'), ('PERSON', 'Public'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MLAs')]
[('GPE', 'Reservation')]
[('GPE', 'Wat')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Maharashtra'), ('GPE', 'Poisonous')]
[('GPE', 'Reality')]
[('GPE', 'Legitimate')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Goa'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NorthEast')]
[('GPE', 'Yeah')]
[('GPE', 'Govt')]
[('GPE', 'Ignore')]
[('GPE', 'Market')]
[('PERSON', 'Karen Johar')]
[('PERSON', 'Twitter')]
[('GPE', 'Israel')]
[('GPE', 'Wrong')]
[('GPE', 'Please'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LOC')]
[('GPE', 'Tanya'), ('GPE', 'Mau'), ('PERSON', 'Fund Manager Academy'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Secret'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KONTINIU'), ('PERSON', 'Cara Profit Secara'), ('PERSON', 'Caranya'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Trading Forex'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'WhatsApp')]
[('PERSON', 'Sanghi'), ('PERSON', 'Kejriwal'), ('PERSON', 'Anna'), ('PERSON', 'Gandhi')]
[('GPE', 'Manumasti')]
[('PERSON', 'Putin'), ('PERSON', 'Trump'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Rahul So')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PAK'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PAKISTAN')]
[('GPE', 'Send'), ('PERSON', 'Rakshk')]
[('GPE', 'Fatwa'), ('GPE', 'Fake')]
[('GPE', 'Petrol')]
[('GPE', 'Long'), ('PERSON', 'Bought')]
[('PERSON', 'Sindhi'), ('PERSON', 'Shivraj Singh Chouhan')]
[('GPE', 'Middle East')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Prince Fadii'), ('GPE', 'April'), ('PERSON', 'Auto Comment')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Fatwa'), ('PERSON', 'Nahid Afreen'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fatwa')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'VIPs')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Federal')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP'), ('GPE', 'SImple')]
[('GPE', 'Horrible')]
[('GPE', 'Fake')]
[('GPE', 'Nope')]
[('PERSON', 'Maruti Suzuki'), ('GPE', 'Alambagh'), ('PERSON', 'Vitara Breeza'), ('PERSON', 'Lucknow'), ('GPE', 'Dealer'), ('PERSON', 'Vehicle Registration No'), ('PERSON', 'Oneup Moters Arambagh')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Bed')]
[('GPE', 'Modi')]
[('GPE', 'Seema')]
[('PERSON', 'Aggar Dear Sir'), ('GPE', 'Pl'), ('PERSON', 'Amitj')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CNBC')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BTW'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NOT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GOD')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Laws'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FCC'), ('PERSON', 'Which')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Flavour'), ('PERSON', 'Sunny Leone'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'STD')]
[('GPE', 'Request'), ('PERSON', 'Pak Army')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NDTV')]
[('PERSON', 'Guarav K'), ('GPE', 'Yak')]
[('PERSON', 'Donald Trump'), ('GPE', 'Waw')]
[('GPE', 'Coke'), ('PERSON', 'Abfrl Future')]
[('PERSON', 'Arunachal Pradesh'), ('PERSON', 'Gyatso'), ('GPE', 'Beijing'), ('PERSON', 'Tenzin')]
[('GPE', 'South'), ('PERSON', 'Q2')]
[('GPE', 'PAKISTANAN')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI')]
[('PERSON', 'Sanjiv')]
[('GPE', 'Bro')]
[('PERSON', 'Mohamed'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Sira'), ('PERSON', 'Kafirs'), ('PERSON', 'Jay'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Ledo'), ('PERSON', 'Islam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Koran'), ('PERSON', 'Jizya')]
[('GPE', 'Yeah')]
[('GPE', 'Shame')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Secularism'), ('GPE', 'Hinduism'), ('PERSON', 'Let')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'TIME'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'STRICT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THEM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FIND'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NEW'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TO'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CHRONIC')]
[('GPE', 'Yellow')]
[('GPE', 'Dim')]
[('GPE', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Rupees')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Didi'), ('PERSON', 'Mulayam'), ('PERSON', 'Laloo')]
[('PERSON', 'Kudos'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Beauty'), ('LOCATION', 'Beast'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Proud'), ('GPE', 'TATA')]
[('GPE', 'Bloody')]
[('PERSON', 'Nehru'), ('PERSON', 'Anna'), ('PERSON', 'Gandhi')]
[('GPE', 'Please'), ('GPE', 'Bollywood')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Raju'), ('GPE', 'Good'), ('GPE', 'Shameful')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindus')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Return'), ('PERSON', 'Order India'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Narendra Modi'), ('PERSON', 'Recep Tayyip Erdoan'), ('GPE', 'Turkey')]
[('GPE', 'South'), ('PERSON', 'Q2')]
[('GPE', 'Cancel')]
[('GPE', 'Mrng')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Parliament')]
[('GPE', 'Future'), ('GPE', 'Serious'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Jagran')]
[('GPE', 'Navaratri')]
[('GPE', 'Humble')]
[('PERSON', 'Laws'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FCC'), ('PERSON', 'Which')]
[('GPE', 'Sycophancy')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Rahul')]
[('GPE', 'Sir'), ('PERSON', 'Sadness')]
[('GPE', 'Govt'), ('GPE', 'Society'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Voiceindia'), ('GPE', 'System'), ('PERSON', 'Jai'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DAMINI')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('PERSON', 'Does'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Delhi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AK'), ('PERSON', 'Anna Hazare'), ('PERSON', 'Anna'), ('GPE', 'Lokpal'), ('PERSON', 'Aap'), ('PERSON', 'Lokpal')]
[('PERSON', 'Mr. Naarendra Modi'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Modi'), ('GPE', 'Proud')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Kiren Bedi'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('GPE', 'Hindu')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ELSE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'POOR')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindu'), ('PERSON', 'Azaan'), ('PERSON', 'Love Marriages'), ('GPE', 'Sonu'), ('PERSON', 'Hindus'), ('PERSON', 'Kashmir'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CNBC'), ('GPE', 'Hahaha')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NDTV')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Plz')]
[('GPE', 'Interest')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CNBC')]
[('PERSON', 'Sorry'), ('PERSON', 'Bjp'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Soldiers')]
[('GPE', 'Result')]
[('PERSON', 'Falguni'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MIT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CalTech'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Ghosh Protik Biswas')]
[('GPE', 'Vermula')]
[('GPE', 'Good')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Bank'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ATM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CSH')]
[('GPE', 'Han')]
[('GPE', 'Sonu')]
[('PERSON', 'Prithvi'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Setty')]
[('PERSON', 'Jio')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Bollywood'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Kumar'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Ashis')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Social'), ('PERSON', 'Dear')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Mandirs'), ('PERSON', 'Nigam'), ('PERSON', 'Azaan'), ('PERSON', 'Sonu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Jagarans'), ('GPE', 'Gurudwara')]
[('GPE', 'Italy'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Islamic'), ('GPE', 'England'), ('GPE', 'Muslim'), ('PERSON', 'Sikhs'), ('GPE', 'Saudi'), ('GPE', 'Kenya'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Hell'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Cole Bombers'), ('GPE', 'Scripture'), ('PERSON', 'Jemaah Islamiyah'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Boston Marathon'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'INJUSTICE'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('FACILITY', 'Air France Entebbe'), ('PERSON', 'Jihad'), ('PERSON', 'Hindus'), ('GPE', 'Nigeria'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Embassy Bombers'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MUSLIMS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ISLAMIC'), ('PERSON', 'Musiims'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Beirut Marine Barracks'), ('PERSON', 'Abdullah Azzam Brigades'), ('PERSON', 'Allah'), ('GPE', 'Germany'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Jews'), ('PERSON', 'Christians'), ('PERSON', 'Alif'), ('GPE', 'Moscow'), ('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'USA'), ('GPE', 'Sudan'), ('PERSON', 'Don'), ('PERSON', 'Shintos'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Buenos Aires Suicide'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Beirut U.S. Embassy'), ('GPE', 'Besian'), ('GPE', 'France'), ('GPE', 'Buddhists'), ('GPE', 'Sabians'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Achille Lauro Cruise Ship'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Bafi Nightclub'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Embassy Takeover'), ('GPE', 'Afghanistan'), ('GPE', 'Lebanon'), ('PERSON', 'Muslim'), ('PERSON', 'Allah Knows'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'London Subway Bombers'), ('GPE', 'Libya'), ('PERSON', 'Lam'), ('PERSON', 'Jew'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Beltway Snipers'), ('GPE', 'Israeli'), ('PERSON', 'Islam'), ('PERSON', 'Mumbai India'), ('GPE', 'Belgium'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Shoe'), ('GPE', 'Sweden'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Kenyan U.S'), ('GPE', 'Quran'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Libyan U.S. Embassy'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Airline'), ('PERSON', 'Islamic'), ('GSP', 'Syria'), ('GPE', 'Yemen'), ('GPE', 'Iraq'), ('GPE', 'Egypt'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Hindus'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Bombay'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Madrid Train'), ('GPE', 'Polytheists'), ('PERSON', 'Atheists'), ('GPE', 'Allah'), ('GPE', 'Australia'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Scripture'), ('GPE', 'Jains'), ('PERSON', 'Muslim Brotherhood'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Islam'), ('GPE', 'Iranian'), ('GPE', 'Iran'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fort Hood'), ('PERSON', 'Khobar Towers Bombers'), ('PERSON', 'Buddhists'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THIS'), ('GPE', 'Christian')]
[('PERSON', 'Natalie')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ATM')]
[('PERSON', 'Gauri Khan'), ('PERSON', 'Sussaine')]
[('GPE', 'Happy'), ('GPE', 'Jolly')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'GLENMARK'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TRADE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AND'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BUY')]
[('PERSON', 'Udayan Mukherjee')]
[('PERSON', 'Riya')]
[('PERSON', 'Tom'), ('GPE', 'Kolkata'), ('PERSON', 'Jerry')]
[('PERSON', 'Jokes'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Commenting Suvarna')]
[('GPE', 'Idiot'), ('GPE', 'Wer')]
[('GPE', 'Eleven'), ('PERSON', 'Abhay'), ('GPE', 'Nagpur')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PM')]
[('PERSON', 'Islamic State')]
[('GPE', 'Kejriwal'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Farah Khan')]
[('GPE', 'Long')]
[('PERSON', 'Dam'), ('PERSON', 'Furious'), ('PERSON', 'Say'), ('LOCATION', 'South China'), ('GPE', 'China Fast'), ('GPE', 'Indus'), ('PERSON', 'Us India Need Be'), ('PERSON', 'Jawaharlal Nehru'), ('GPE', 'China'), ('PERSON', 'Never Going'), ('PERSON', 'Union Territories'), ('PERSON', 'Indus Waters Treaty'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Of India'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Claim South China Sea China Made'), ('PERSON', 'Ability'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Bark'), ('PERSON', 'Keep Quit'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Jawaharlal Nehru'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Will Blame Us'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ScrapIndusWatersTreaty Indus'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Partys And Also With Our Useless Politician'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'World Bank')]
[('PERSON', 'Kejriwal')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Shayad')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'News')]
[('PERSON', 'Well')]
[('GPE', 'Everyone')]
[('PERSON', 'Rajasthan'), ('GPE', 'Maharastra'), ('GPE', 'Karnataka'), ('PERSON', 'Ban'), ('PERSON', 'Tamil Nadu')]
[('GPE', 'Maharashtra'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Sonia Gandhi'), ('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('PERSON', 'Rahul Gandhi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('GPE', 'Nanded')]
[('GPE', 'Does')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Azadi')]
[('GPE', 'Tata'), ('GPE', 'Ratan'), ('PERSON', 'Tata')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'UP'), ('GPE', 'Rolta'), ('GPE', 'Good')]
[('GPE', 'Prabhas'), ('GPE', 'Prabhaas'), ('GPE', 'Credit')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS Sevak')]
[('GPE', 'France'), ('GPE', 'Paris'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP Goon')]
[('GPE', 'Hindus')]
[('GPE', 'Hindu'), ('GPE', 'Asrar')]
[('PERSON', 'Pawan Goenka'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BS4')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Neerat'), ('PERSON', 'Misha'), ('PERSON', 'Basically')]
[('GPE', 'Gunda'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Yogi'), ('PERSON', 'Jungle Raj UP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LoC')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SELL'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RATE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LOT')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'USA'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Suresh Prabhu'), ('PERSON', 'Rail Budget'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Pay Commission')]
[('PERSON', 'Aazaan')]
[('GPE', 'Great')]
[('PERSON', 'Bhakts'), ('GPE', 'Respect'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('PERSON', 'Shah'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Democracy')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Smart')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('PERSON', 'Donald Trump'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'US'), ('PERSON', 'Lahore Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Expert'), ('PERSON', 'Trump'), ('PERSON', 'Ghatib Ali Shad')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Kunder'), ('GPE', 'Shirish')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LICENSE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NEEDS'), ('GPE', 'INDIA')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'News'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ISIS')]
[('GPE', 'Lol')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MPs')]
[('PERSON', 'Jan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Mistry'), ('GPE', 'Cyrus'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Companies Act')]
[('PERSON', 'Tamil Nadu')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'HCC')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'REAL'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LIFE')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BAT'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Army'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Krishna Ghatti'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Buttal'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Antonio Conte')]
[('GPE', 'Shewag'), ('PERSON', 'Dawood')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Drammebaj'), ('PERSON', 'Lok Pal'), ('PERSON', 'Annaji')]
[('GPE', 'Live')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LOL')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Arvind Subramaniyam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PM'), ('PERSON', 'Adhia')]
[('GPE', 'Stupidity')]
[('GPE', 'Media'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CLap Clap')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslim')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Met Gala')]
[('GPE', 'Wow')]
[('GPE', 'Shame'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Abp')]
[('GPE', 'Dumb')]
[('PERSON', 'Vinod'), ('PERSON', 'Pakistani')]
[('PERSON', 'Al Zawahiri'), ('GPE', 'Osama')]
[('GPE', 'Indians')]
[('PERSON', 'Jitu Rai'), ('PERSON', 'Air Pistol'), ('GPE', 'New Delhi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ISSF'), ('PERSON', 'Clinching Gold'), ('PERSON', 'Heena Sidhu Delighted')]
[('PERSON', 'Own Respectable PM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Own')]
[('PERSON', 'Mohamed'), ('PERSON', 'Eric'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Lopez'), ('GPE', 'Islam'), ('PERSON', 'Islam')]
[('PERSON', 'Electric Power')]
[('GPE', 'Porinju')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'GOI')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'VHP')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GDP')]
[('PERSON', 'Singh'), ('PERSON', 'Arnav')]
[('GPE', 'Kangaroo'), ('PERSON', 'Zulfikar Ali Bhutto')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindus')]
[('GPE', 'Build'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Shahs'), ('PERSON', 'Hyderabad')]
[('GPE', 'Lol')]
[('PERSON', 'Jesus Christ Amen'), ('PERSON', 'Christian')]
[('PERSON', 'Priyank'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Bhardwaj')]
[('GPE', 'Money')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistani')]
[('PERSON', 'Reema'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GATI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'WELSPUN')]
[('GPE', 'Abe')]
[('GPE', 'INDIA')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Hazare'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PPP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PTI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ICJ')]
[('PERSON', 'Dalit'), ('PERSON', 'Muslims')]
[('GPE', 'Batkha')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Alam'), ('GPE', 'Israr')]
[('PERSON', 'Mr.')]
[('PERSON', 'Wasim Hassan'), ('PERSON', 'Rape')]
[('PERSON', 'Anti Against'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UP'), ('PERSON', 'Indian Express')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ONLY'), ('GPE', 'INDIAN'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NOT'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Karara')]
[('GPE', 'Modiji'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'Thank')]
[('PERSON', 'Good Job')]
[('PERSON', 'Carbodrum'), ('GPE', 'Please'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Intellect')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Ahsan'), ('PERSON', 'Correct'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Royal Enfield')]
[('PERSON', 'Virat Kohli'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KL Rahul'), ('PERSON', 'Ajinkya Rahane')]
[('GPE', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Mar')]
[('GPE', 'Lol'), ('PERSON', 'Don')]
[('GPE', 'Feel')]
[('GPE', 'Hope'), ('GPE', 'Good')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Priyanka Gandhi'), ('PERSON', 'Shri Rahul Gandhi')]
[('GPE', 'Kajol')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Met Gala')]
[('PERSON', 'Ninda')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PANEL'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'STEP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'COMMON'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'wOULD'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PARTIES')]
[('PERSON', 'Nitin Gadkari')]
[('GPE', 'Great'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Initiative')]
[('PERSON', 'Indian Express'), ('GPE', 'Great')]
[('GPE', 'Fake')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MODI')]
[('PERSON', 'Kejriwal'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'JSW')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'STFU')]
[('GPE', 'Pakisthan'), ('PERSON', 'Pakisthan')]
[('GPE', 'Hahahha')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Natural Resources')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'GDP')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PM Sh'), ('GPE', 'Kashmir'), ('PERSON', 'Modi Ji'), ('PERSON', 'Terrorist')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('PERSON', 'Sonia Gandhi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ICJ'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindu')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'US Bond'), ('GSP', 'US'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IntrestRate'), ('PERSON', 'Stocks')]
[('GPE', 'Want'), ('GPE', 'Swiss'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GDP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ONGC')]
[('GPE', 'Great'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Digvijay Singhs'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Traitors'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Patriotism')]
[('GPE', 'Abhi')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Hindutva'), ('GPE', 'Rishabh'), ('GPE', 'Ram'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Express'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PM Modi')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Twitter')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims')]
[('PERSON', 'Rajeev'), ('PERSON', 'Pillai')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Supreme')]
[('GPE', 'Ha')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslim')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Range')]
[('GPE', 'Frailty')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Debate')]
[('PERSON', 'Congrat'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Reserve Bank')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Jay')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('PERSON', 'Kadiyala Sushanth Chandra'), ('PERSON', 'Sankeerth')]
[('GPE', 'Only'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Taliban')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Divisional'), ('GPE', 'Hain'), ('PERSON', 'Matlab Hai'), ('PERSON', 'Karne'), ('PERSON', 'Muslim')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Salman Khursid'), ('PERSON', 'Mani S. Iyar')]
[('GPE', 'Stop'), ('GPE', 'Dude')]
[('PERSON', 'Lokpal')]
[('GPE', 'Indians')]
[('GPE', 'Common')]
[('PERSON', 'Sushma Swaraj')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'DTAA'), ('PERSON', 'Growth')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Miksau'), ('PERSON', 'Stay')]
[('GPE', 'Feel'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Afzal Guru'), ('PERSON', 'Rahul Gandhi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('PERSON', 'Sonu Nigam'), ('PERSON', 'Akrabuddin Owaisi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('LOCATION', 'North'), ('GPE', 'Keralas'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim'), ('GPE', 'Korean')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MLA'), ('GPE', 'Yogi')]
[('GPE', 'Modi'), ('PERSON', 'Amit'), ('GPE', 'God')]
[('PERSON', 'Moron')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslims')]
[('PERSON', 'Infosys Chairman')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP'), ('PERSON', 'Delhi'), ('PERSON', 'Hope')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'YOUR'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'EXPRESS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'INDIAN'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'POSITION OF'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'COMMENTS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CONGRESS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AND'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PL'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MAJORITY')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Does')]
[('GPE', 'Savage')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Happy'), ('PERSON', 'Kabul Afghanistan')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Had'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UPA')]
[('GPE', 'Indian'), ('GPE', 'Lahore'), ('PERSON', 'Jatin Jitin Kapoor'), ('GPE', 'Pakistanis'), ('GPE', 'Pakistani'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Pakistani')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'STUPID'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'INFLUENCE OF'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CITIZEN OF'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NOT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PARTY'), ('GPE', 'Rome'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RELIGION')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NSG')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Afghanistan'), ('PERSON', 'Afghan'), ('GPE', 'Long')]
[('GPE', 'Good')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Pakistanis'), ('GPE', 'Lahore')]
[('GPE', 'Time')]
[('GPE', 'Safety')]
[('GPE', 'Men'), ('GPE', 'Nobody')]
[('GPE', 'Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RTI')]
[('PERSON', 'Enfield')]
[('GPE', 'Jb'), ('PERSON', 'Aram'), ('PERSON', 'Lokpaal Lokpaal Bolte'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Jee'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'Bring'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Twitter'), ('PERSON', 'Antony')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('GPE', 'Gau'), ('PERSON', 'Muslims')]
[('GPE', 'Waste'), ('GPE', 'Nothing'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Maharashtra'), ('PERSON', 'Mumbai Everywhere')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS')]
[('GPE', 'Saitan'), ('GPE', 'Hindus')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'Please')]
[('GPE', 'Bastar'), ('GPE', 'Rohit')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'GST')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ABP Ananda'), ('PERSON', 'Sanchari'), ('PERSON', 'Bikram')]
[('GPE', 'Save')]
[('GPE', 'Lol'), ('GPE', 'America')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LoL'), ('PERSON', 'Rahul')]
[('PERSON', 'Pakistani'), ('GPE', 'Byta')]
[('PERSON', 'Tamilnadu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JJ'), ('PERSON', 'Annadurai MGR'), ('PERSON', 'Kamaraj')]
[('GPE', 'Trump')]
[('GPE', 'Hmare')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Royal Enfield')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Africans')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LOC'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'HAHAHAHAHA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Occupied Kashmir'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Jansatta'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PM Modi'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Prateek Nishant'), ('PERSON', 'Mr.')]
[('GPE', 'Beef'), ('GPE', 'Hinduism'), ('GPE', 'Rigveda'), ('PERSON', 'Vashistha Dharmasutra'), ('PERSON', 'Brahma'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Cow Mata'), ('PERSON', 'Indra'), ('GPE', 'Shatpath Brahmin'), ('GPE', 'Cow'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Brahmin')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('PERSON', 'Abhishek Biswas'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BHIM'), ('PERSON', 'Mr.')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Pvt'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FYI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CONG'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ISRO'), ('GPE', 'List'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Computrise'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'International')]
[('GPE', 'Sir'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PSU'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'STC'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MMTC')]
[('PERSON', 'Kadi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BULL')]
[('PERSON', 'Deep Ind'), ('GPE', 'Alphageo')]
[('GPE', 'Fake')]
[('GPE', 'Colour')]
[('GPE', 'Idiot')]
[('PERSON', 'Shoaib'), ('PERSON', 'Khan Lughmani')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CNBC'), ('PERSON', 'Dear')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'FM Jeithley')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SBI')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Democratic')]
[('PERSON', 'Kashmir Issue'), ('PERSON', 'Turkey Will')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindi'), ('GPE', 'Kejariwal')]
[('GPE', 'Dont'), ('PERSON', 'Feel')]
[('GPE', 'Yess')]
[('GPE', 'Speechs')]
[('PERSON', 'Hook'), ('GPE', 'Hindustan')]
[('PERSON', 'Tim Worstall'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FORBES'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GDP')]
[('GPE', 'Lol'), ('GPE', 'Pakistani')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Election Commission'), ('GPE', 'Donate'), ('PERSON', 'Sabha Election'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ENJOY'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RTI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ECI'), ('GPE', 'People'), ('GPE', 'Answer'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RP')]
[('GPE', 'Tamil')]
[('GPE', 'Dont'), ('GPE', 'Same')]
[('GPE', 'Cow')]
[('GPE', 'Smart')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Yup')]
[('GPE', 'Sonu')]
[('PERSON', 'Aur'), ('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('PERSON', 'Kar'), ('PERSON', 'Rahey'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'SADHUS'), ('PERSON', 'Sanyasis')]
[('GPE', 'Great')]
[('GPE', 'Mumbai'), ('PERSON', 'Shiv'), ('PERSON', 'Air India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Sena')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SnakeEagle Pakistan Defence Command'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'Banks'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Customer')]
[('GPE', 'Wait'), ('GPE', 'Kamin')]
[('GPE', 'Look')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MIT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'University'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IIT')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('GPE', 'Awareness')]
[('PERSON', 'Azaan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CallMeByYourName'), ('PERSON', 'Shubhra Gupta'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ENTERTAINMENT')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'Nitin'), ('PERSON', 'Montek')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Ishaq Zada'), ('GPE', 'May'), ('PERSON', 'Auto Comment'), ('PERSON', 'Poke Me')]
[('PERSON', 'Devs'), ('GPE', 'Sonia')]
[('GPE', 'Doctor')]
[('GPE', 'Hindu')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Digviajy')]
[('GPE', 'Simply')]
[('PERSON', 'Varanasi')]
[('GPE', 'Nice')]
[('GPE', 'Ashish')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'DREAMS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SLEEPING'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MAKE')]
[('GPE', 'Fake')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JANTA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'HAI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'DESH')]
[('PERSON', 'Sak Soft'), ('PERSON', 'Dilip Bhat'), ('PERSON', 'Aksh Optimizer')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'YASH')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Mediocrity')]
[('PERSON', 'Bahan'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Kitne'), ('GPE', 'Bihar')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'TOI'), ('GPE', 'East'), ('GPE', 'Meerut'), ('GPE', 'Nation'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Original Party'), ('PERSON', 'Multiple Madarassa'), ('PERSON', 'Kerala Vande Matram Kand'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Secular Party'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NIRBHAYA'), ('GPE', 'Loni'), ('PERSON', 'Ghaziabad'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Media'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muh'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress Govt'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UP Govt')]
[('GPE', 'BEST'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PATRIOTISM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FOOD'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TEST OF'), ('GPE', 'BRITISH'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PEOPLE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LET')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP')]
[('PERSON', 'Person')]
[('PERSON', 'Fascism'), ('GPE', 'Amazing'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Obama'), ('PERSON', 'Trump')]
[('PERSON', 'Shyam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Nath')]
[('GPE', 'Thanks')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RE')]
[('PERSON', 'Son'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan PM'), ('PERSON', 'Maryam Nawaz Sharif')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'GDP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'INR')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MLA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Democracy'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Hence')]
[('PERSON', 'Poor')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Join')]
[('GPE', 'VYAPAM')]
[('GPE', 'Prayer'), ('PERSON', 'Namaaz'), ('GPE', 'Azaan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'WITHOUT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SENSEX'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SEE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'FLEW'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NOT')]
[('GPE', 'Deepak')]
[('GPE', 'Sir')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Yogi'), ('GPE', 'Totaly'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Adityanath'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ABP News'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Comment')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Kangana'), ('PERSON', 'Love')]
[('GPE', 'CNBC'), ('PERSON', 'Arnab Goswani')]
[('PERSON', 'Islam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MCD')]
[('GPE', 'Kiran'), ('GPE', 'Nation'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Gen')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Maoist'), ('PERSON', 'Maoist')]
[('GPE', 'Salman')]
[('GPE', 'Always')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Delhi')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindus'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Hindu')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Plz'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UPA2'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UPA1')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ABVP')]
[('GPE', 'Ratish'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Menon')]
[('PERSON', 'Defame Them'), ('GPE', 'New India'), ('PERSON', 'Match Modi So Easy Way')]
[('GPE', 'Diwali'), ('GPE', 'Anuj'), ('GPE', 'Tune')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'WHOLE'), ('PERSON', 'Rahul')]
[('GPE', 'Kejri'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Kejri'), ('GPE', 'Department')]
[('GPE', 'Sook')]
[('PERSON', 'Fatwa'), ('PERSON', 'Nahid Afreen'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fatwa')]
[('GPE', 'Please')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Appreciate Good')]
[('PERSON', 'Wipro')]
[('GPE', 'North East'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ONLY'), ('GPE', 'Chaddi'), ('PERSON', 'Goa'), ('GPE', 'Goa')]
[('GPE', 'Media'), ('GPE', 'Randia')]
[('PERSON', 'Visa'), ('PERSON', 'Master'), ('GPE', 'Shame'), ('PERSON', 'Reliance Jio Money'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Corporate Social'), ('GPE', 'Paytm'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CSR')]
[('PERSON', 'Chandra')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Sunder'), ('PERSON', 'Satya'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('PERSON', 'Rations'), ('GPE', 'Kerala')]
[('PERSON', 'Aditya'), ('PERSON', 'Kumar Acharya')]
[('GPE', 'Pak'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Pak'), ('GPE', 'Revenge')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Human Brain'), ('PERSON', 'Zero Science'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MAGIC')]
[('GPE', 'Sir')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'USA')]
[('PERSON', 'Jai Hind'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Modi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Good Stocks'), ('PERSON', 'Will')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SINDU'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'PDS'), ('PERSON', 'Dictator')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindu')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan')]
[('GPE', 'News'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'From Jansatta')]
[('PERSON', 'Sorrell'), ('GSP', 'US'), ('PERSON', 'Trump')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Agree')]
[('GPE', 'Hindu')]
[('PERSON', 'Lalita S'), ('GPE', 'Great'), ('PERSON', 'Antonio')]
[('PERSON', 'Mohanty'), ('GPE', 'Chinmay')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Azan'), ('PERSON', 'Eid'), ('PERSON', 'Hanuman Jayanti'), ('PERSON', 'Muslim Azan'), ('PERSON', 'Vashi Sharma Agniveer'), ('GPE', 'Muharram'), ('GPE', 'Agniveer'), ('GPE', 'Aarti'), ('PERSON', 'Hanuman Yatra'), ('PERSON', 'Ganesh Chaturthi'), ('GPE', 'Azan'), ('PERSON', 'Prophet'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('PERSON', 'Ganesh Yatra'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Aarti'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim'), ('GPE', 'Look'), ('PERSON', 'Hindu Aarti'), ('GPE', 'Zero')]
[('GPE', 'Reduce')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MLA')]
[('PERSON', 'Mr.')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Panthoiren Only'), ('PERSON', 'Rajkumar')]
[('PERSON', 'Pharma Sector')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Erdugan'), ('GPE', 'Indians'), ('PERSON', 'Muslim')]
[('PERSON', 'Rajiv Gandhi Equity')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'DailyO'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Express'), ('GPE', 'Viral'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Jandhan')]
[('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Muslims'), ('GPE', 'Hazimastan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Hindus'), ('PERSON', 'Gulshan Kumar'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim'), ('GPE', 'Dawoodz'), ('PERSON', 'Modi G'), ('GPE', 'Congressis')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Rohtak'), ('GPE', 'Haryana'), ('GPE', 'Useless')]
[('GPE', 'Bjp'), ('GPE', 'Uttar')]
[('GPE', 'Keep')]
[('PERSON', 'Kalpesh Jain'), ('PERSON', 'Edelweiss'), ('GPE', 'Bharti')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NGOs'), ('PERSON', 'Leftist'), ('PERSON', 'Dear'), ('PERSON', 'Narendra Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MSM'), ('GPE', 'Screw')]
[('GPE', 'Sonia')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP Party'), ('PERSON', 'Amit'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('GPE', 'SA'), ('GPE', 'Ask')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('GPE', 'Mumbai'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Karachi'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Muslim'), ('PERSON', 'Islam')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'CNBC'), ('PERSON', 'Mukesh Ambani')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Express'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Whole')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'HyDer'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BTW'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Khoso Common')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('GPE', 'Turkey'), ('PERSON', 'Sikhs'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KashmirIssue'), ('GPE', 'Simple')]
[('PERSON', 'Fatwa'), ('PERSON', 'Nahid Afreen'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fatwa')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Sir'), ('PERSON', 'Janlokpal')]
[('GPE', 'Poor')]
[('GPE', 'Russia'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UBI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'No')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Navraate'), ('GPE', 'Azaans'), ('PERSON', 'Festival')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistani')]
[('GPE', 'Jio')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('PERSON', 'Rahul Gandhi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP Express'), ('PERSON', 'Anti')]
[('PERSON', 'Johar'), ('PERSON', 'Karan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KanganaRanaut')]
[('PERSON', 'Dena')]
[('GPE', 'Lok')]
[('GPE', 'Reliance'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Relcapital')]
[('GPE', 'Good')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'Ayodhia'), ('PERSON', 'Babri Masjid'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Akhil Bhratiya Hind Mahsabh'), ('PERSON', 'Bajrang Dal'), ('GPE', 'Muslims'), ('GPE', 'Jerusalem'), ('GPE', 'Allah'), ('PERSON', 'Quresh Tribes'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('PERSON', 'Allah'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'House'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'VHP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Makkah'), ('PERSON', 'Masjid'), ('PERSON', 'Allah Masjid'), ('PERSON', 'Holy Quran'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Zionist Israel'), ('PERSON', 'Madinah')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'THE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'RIDE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CLOSURE OF')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ICJ')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ITC Ltd')]
[('GPE', 'Hypocrisy'), ('PERSON', 'Bjp')]
[('PERSON', 'Allah')]
[('GPE', 'Wait')]
[('GPE', 'AiADMK'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KILL'), ('GPE', 'INDIA'), ('GPE', 'Palaniswami'), ('PERSON', 'Panneerselvam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CORRUPTION'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AIADMK'), ('PERSON', 'Tamil Nadu'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CHANCE')]
[('GPE', 'Shame'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('GPE', 'Nobody'), ('GPE', 'British'), ('GPE', 'Idiotic')]
[('PERSON', 'Shahid')]
[('GPE', 'Nope'), ('PERSON', 'Sadat'), ('GPE', 'Bahubali')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Parliament')]
[('PERSON', 'Amma'), ('GPE', 'Rest'), ('GPE', 'Tamilnadu'), ('GPE', 'Peace')]
[('PERSON', 'Pakistani'), ('GPE', 'Cousin'), ('GPE', 'Btw')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim Country'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Look'), ('PERSON', 'Hahahhahaha')]
[('GPE', 'Ignore'), ('GPE', 'Indian'), ('GPE', 'Muslim')]
[('PERSON', 'Well')]
[('PERSON', 'Facebook'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Sony')]
[('PERSON', 'Steve Jobs')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'GST')]
[('GPE', 'Thn')]
[('GPE', 'Malaysia'), ('GPE', 'Indonesia'), ('GPE', 'Kosovo')]
[('PERSON', 'Trumph'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Zeenews'), ('GPE', 'Ask'), ('PERSON', 'Modi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Bjp')]
[('GPE', 'Thank')]
[('GPE', 'Violence'), ('GPE', 'Media')]
[('GPE', 'Looks')]
[('PERSON', 'Jogis')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP')]
[('GPE', 'Diggi')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Advocate'), ('PERSON', 'Sushma'), ('GPE', 'Good')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SS'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MFs')]
[('GPE', 'Indias'), ('PERSON', 'Hindi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'LOC'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Sonu'), ('PERSON', 'Agree')]
[('PERSON', 'Ribak'), ('PERSON', 'Imdat EVM'), ('PERSON', 'Delhi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'AAPTARDS'), ('GPE', 'Punjab')]
[('GPE', 'English')]
[('PERSON', 'Amazon')]
[('PERSON', 'Shamvil'), ('PERSON', 'Hasan Kazmi')]
[('GPE', 'Indians')]
[('GPE', 'Market')]
[('GPE', 'Unitech'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TATA'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JP')]
[('GPE', 'Muslims')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Alleppo'), ('GPE', 'Damascus'), ('GSP', 'Syria')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'YouTube')]
[('GPE', 'Great')]
[('GPE', 'China Europe')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI')]
[('GPE', 'Money'), ('GPE', 'Hi')]
[('GPE', 'Hindus')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Nse'), ('PERSON', 'Buy'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JAYBARMARU')]
[('GPE', 'Needs')]
[('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('PERSON', 'Rahul')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Cleverness'), ('GPE', 'Kashmir'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Hah'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ShameIE')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'GM'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'OnePlus India'), ('PERSON', 'Vikas Agarwal')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Sonu Remembers Shahbaz Ali Sayyed'), ('PERSON', 'Sonu Nigham')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'GREAT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'THE'), ('PERSON', 'Mooodiijiiie'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GDP')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Supreme Court')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Yamuna'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Comment')]
[('PERSON', 'Khakhi')]
[('GPE', 'Eicher'), ('GPE', 'Bullet')]
[('GPE', 'China'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JIN'), ('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Boycott'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NSG'), ('GPE', 'Chinese'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'XI'), ('PERSON', 'Pakistani'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'HUGE')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Azaan'), ('GPE', 'Ganpati'), ('GPE', 'Problem')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Rahul'), ('PERSON', 'Kejriwal'), ('GPE', 'Sonia')]
[('GPE', 'Foolish'), ('GPE', 'Believe'), ('GPE', 'Nobody')]
[('GPE', 'Happy'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NDFC')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SHAKSHI'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MILLION'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MEDALIST'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'ONLY'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'GREAT'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'SINDHU')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Lotus')]
[('GPE', 'Pls')]
[('GPE', 'Gud')]
[('PERSON', 'Vashikaran')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'UNFOLLOW')]
[('PERSON', 'Zee'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'TRP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'CRPF'), ('GPE', 'Punjab'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'News')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'KKR')]
[('GPE', 'Baluchistan'), ('PERSON', 'Army'), ('GPE', 'Public')]
[('GPE', 'UP')]
[('GPE', 'Shruthi')]
[('PERSON', 'Reason')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Shikha Sharma'), ('GPE', 'Farm')]
[('GPE', 'Turkey'), ('GPE', 'Erdogan')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BSF')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('GPE', 'Jadhav'), ('PERSON', 'Sartaz')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan Army'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Black')]
[('PERSON', 'Sad')]
[('PERSON', 'Air Pollution')]
[('PERSON', 'Petrol'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Saudi Arabia'), ('PERSON', 'Islam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('GPE', 'Deference')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Airtel')]
[('GPE', 'Ad')]
[('GPE', 'Lol')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Har'), ('PERSON', 'Muslim')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BURNAL')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SRS Ltd')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI')]
[('PERSON', 'Suzlon')]
[('PERSON', 'Tum')]
[('GPE', 'Shut')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Delhi')]
[('PERSON', 'Mamata')]
[('PERSON', 'Singh'), ('PERSON', 'Keynes'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Parliament')]
[('PERSON', 'Lions'), ('PERSON', 'Uddhav'), ('GPE', 'Bjp')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('GPE', 'Kerala')]
[('PERSON', 'Sardar Vallabhbhai'), ('GPE', 'Real')]
[('GPE', 'Media'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Kashmiri Separatists')]
[('GPE', 'Tiger')]
[('PERSON', 'Manipur'), ('PERSON', 'Goa'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'UP'), ('PERSON', 'Punjab')]
[('PERSON', 'Fatwa'), ('PERSON', 'Nahid Afreen'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Fatwa')]
[('GPE', 'Kerala')]
[('GPE', 'Totaly')]
[('GPE', 'Natak')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Doggy'), ('PERSON', 'Isis')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBI'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Rajan'), ('PERSON', 'Indias RBI')]
[('PERSON', 'Quora')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'TATA')]
[('PERSON', 'Mr. Eric')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Army'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('PERSON', 'Azan')]
[('GPE', 'Asian'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Market')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Express'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Festival')]
[('PERSON', 'Biggest'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP Funding'), ('GPE', 'Pls'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Loot')]
[('GPE', 'Pak'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Ahmedzai'), ('GPE', 'Afghani'), ('PERSON', 'Afghani')]
[('GPE', 'Rohitji'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('GPE', 'Guns'), ('GPE', 'Freedom'), ('GPE', 'Jehad')]
[('GSP', 'US'), ('GPE', 'China')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'EASILY'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'EXPIRES'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MEAN')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MMS'), ('PERSON', 'Shekhar')]
[('GPE', 'Dont'), ('PERSON', 'Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'IExpress')]
[('GPE', 'Good')]
[('GPE', 'Host'), ('GPE', 'Hav')]
[('PERSON', 'Anupamp'), ('PERSON', 'Gautam Gambhir')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Giri'), ('PERSON', 'Vikas')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Education')]
[('PERSON', 'Shri'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Glob'), ('PERSON', 'Vaishak S')]
[('PERSON', 'Misha'), ('PERSON', 'Shahid Kapoor')]
[('PERSON', 'Malda'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Express'), ('GPE', 'Indian')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AIB')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BSE'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'MCX')]
[('GPE', 'Indonesia'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Communist')]
[('GPE', 'Nilesh')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'JNU')]
[('GPE', 'Kashmir'), ('GPE', 'Temple')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ATM')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('PERSON', 'Well')]
[('GPE', 'Shame')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Jet Airways')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('PERSON', 'Mr. Modi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Make'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Digital India'), ('PERSON', 'Start')]
[('FACILITY', 'White House'), ('PERSON', 'Starbucks'), ('GPE', 'Americans'), ('PERSON', 'Trump')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Jigar'), ('PERSON', 'Patel')]
[('GPE', 'Baby')]
[('GPE', 'British'), ('PERSON', 'Nehru'), ('GPE', 'Gandhi'), ('GPE', 'Bose')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NDTV'), ('GPE', 'Incomplete')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('PERSON', 'Ill')]
[('GPE', 'Country')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Hindu'), ('PERSON', 'Muslim'), ('GPE', 'Bollywood')]
[('GPE', 'Shem')]
[('PERSON', 'Bahubali'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'KRK'), ('PERSON', 'Mr.')]
[('PERSON', 'Lucknow Metro'), ('GPE', 'Akhilesh')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Shah'), ('PERSON', 'Nilesh')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Richi'), ('PERSON', 'Aggarwal'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'YouTube')]
[('GPE', 'Dekh'), ('GPE', 'Mistry')]
[('GPE', 'East'), ('PERSON', 'Sikhs'), ('PERSON', 'Hindu'), ('GPE', 'Hindustan'), ('PERSON', 'Hinduism'), ('GPE', 'Gandhi'), ('PERSON', 'Gandhi'), ('GPE', 'British'), ('PERSON', 'Hindus'), ('GPE', 'Wast'), ('PERSON', 'Muslim'), ('PERSON', 'Islam'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Islammyat')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Parliament')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'SHOULD'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('PERSON', 'Anna')]
[('PERSON', 'Punjab')]
[('PERSON', 'Rahul'), ('PERSON', 'Bhaiya')]
[('PERSON', 'Lok Sabha')]
[('PERSON', 'Stay'), ('PERSON', 'Ajay'), ('PERSON', 'Singh Baghel Pls')]
[('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Dabba')]
[('PERSON', 'Sonu Nigm')]
[('GPE', 'Change')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'WRONG')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Wat'), ('PERSON', 'Till')]
[('GPE', 'Poor')]
[('GPE', 'Militia')]
[('PERSON', 'Hindus'), ('GPE', 'Cow'), ('GPE', 'Allha')]
[('GPE', 'Guys')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ABVP'), ('PERSON', 'Kanhaiya Kumar')]
[('GPE', 'Sums')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'NBFC'), ('GPE', 'Hi'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'LT Finance'), ('PERSON', 'Rally')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RSS'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP')]
[('GPE', 'Hahahaha')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'BJP'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Pokharan')]
[('GPE', 'Hehe')]
[('GPE', 'Pakistan'), ('PERSON', 'Soviets'), ('GPE', 'Afghanis')]
[('GPE', 'Mayawati')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Turko'), ('PERSON', 'Nazir Taimoor'), ('PERSON', 'Asrar')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PNB')]
[('GPE', 'Great'), ('PERSON', 'Modiji')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'ENTERTAINMENT'), ('PERSON', 'Eric Carroll')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'RBL')]
[('PERSON', 'Swati Mandyal')]
[('PERSON', 'Hard')]
[('PERSON', 'Sanghi')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Congress')]
[('GPE', 'Indian'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'JNU')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'Supreme Court')]
[('GPE', 'Oil'), ('GPE', 'Bloody'), ('PERSON', 'Islam')]
[('GPE', 'Modis')]
[('PERSON', 'Sonia Shenoy')]
[('GPE', 'Russia'), ('GPE', 'America')]
[('PERSON', 'Rule Politics'), ('GPE', 'Divide')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'PM')]
[('GPE', 'NorthEast'), ('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NorthEastern'), ('GPE', 'Proud')]
[('GPE', 'India'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'NLI'), ('PERSON', 'Gilgit Baltistan'), ('PERSON', 'Bajwa')]
[('GPE', 'China'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Islamic')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'MCD')]
[('GPE', 'Clean'), ('GPE', 'India')]
[('GPE', 'Modi')]
[('GPE', 'Rajveer'), ('GPE', 'Girish')]
[('ORGANIZATION', 'AAnisha Porwal')]
[('GPE', 'USSR'), ('GPE', 'North Korea'), ('GPE', 'Vietnam'), ('GPE', 'China')]
[('GPE', 'Manish'), ('PERSON', 'Paul'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Muslim')]
[('GPE', 'Chief')]
[('GPE', 'Religion'), ('PERSON', 'Allow'), ('PERSON', 'Sonu Nigam'), ('PERSON', 'Please'), ('GPE', 'Ban')]
[('PERSON', 'Mukesh Ambani'), ('GPE', 'Jio'), ('GPE', 'New Year')]
[('PERSON', 'Exodus'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Old Testament'), ('ORGANIZATION', 'Semitic')]
